[{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679113911,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":0,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":54493,"timeElapsed":309640},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679135515,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":1,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":21603,"timeElapsed":331244},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679161198,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":2,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":25680,"timeElapsed":356927},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679168020,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":3,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":6821,"timeElapsed":363749},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679175863,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":4,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":47,"rt":7841,"timeElapsed":371592},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679189979,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":5,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":14114,"timeElapsed":385708},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679202961,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":6,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":12981,"timeElapsed":398690},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679225387,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":7,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":22425,"timeElapsed":421116},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679235572,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":8,"questionIdx":0,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"148","question":"Say a word that comes to mind, then say the first word you can think of that starts with the last letter of the word you just said. Keep adding words that start with the last letter of the previous word until you have 25 words. Any words will do–you do not need to make a sentence.","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":10182,"timeElapsed":431301},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679253704,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":9,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":15698,"timeElapsed":449433},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679260624,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":10,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":6919,"timeElapsed":456353},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679265087,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":11,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":4460,"timeElapsed":460816},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679269049,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":12,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":3959,"timeElapsed":464778},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679273555,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":13,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":83,"rt":4504,"timeElapsed":469284},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679281734,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":14,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":8176,"timeElapsed":477463},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679289420,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":15,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7685,"timeElapsed":485149},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679296752,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":16,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":7330,"timeElapsed":492481},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679306509,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":17,"questionIdx":1,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"125","question":"If you were to seek political office, what policies would you run on?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":9755,"timeElapsed":502238},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679324141,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":98,"rt":15566,"timeElapsed":519870},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679334418,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":100,"trialIdx":18,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled HAMBURGER","scaleTextMin":"HOTDOG","scaleTextMax":"HAMBURGER","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10276,"timeElapsed":530147},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679345106,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":19,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":10687,"timeElapsed":540835},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679355142,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":20,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":10035,"timeElapsed":550871},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679358608,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":21,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3463,"timeElapsed":554337},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679361857,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":22,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3247,"timeElapsed":557586},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679368372,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":23,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":89,"rt":6512,"timeElapsed":564101},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679372992,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":24,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":4618,"timeElapsed":568720},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679386523,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":25,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":85,"rt":13529,"timeElapsed":582252},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679390424,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":26,"questionIdx":2,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"133","question":"What person (living or dead) do you most admire or look up to? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":93,"rt":3898,"timeElapsed":586153},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679409736,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":27,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":17550,"timeElapsed":605465},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679416895,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":28,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7157,"timeElapsed":612624},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679422776,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":29,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":5878,"timeElapsed":618504},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679430560,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":30,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":7781,"timeElapsed":626288},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679433727,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":31,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":3164,"timeElapsed":629455},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679442210,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":32,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":8481,"timeElapsed":637939},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679447076,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":33,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":76,"rt":4863,"timeElapsed":642805},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679455709,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":34,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":8629,"timeElapsed":651437},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679459926,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":35,"questionIdx":3,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"63","question":"What do you hope people say about you when you are not in the room?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":4215,"timeElapsed":655655},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679472642,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":36,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":73,"rt":11039,"timeElapsed":668371},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679476787,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":37,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":4143,"timeElapsed":672516},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679482797,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":38,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":61,"rt":6007,"timeElapsed":678526},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679491325,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":39,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":45,"rt":8526,"timeElapsed":687054},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679495110,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":40,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":3784,"timeElapsed":690839},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679502397,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":41,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":7283,"timeElapsed":698126},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679511339,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":42,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":8940,"timeElapsed":707067},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679514459,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":43,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":3119,"timeElapsed":710188},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679517293,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":44,"questionIdx":4,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"188","question":"What is your favorite: ice cream flavor, color, musical instrument, animal, and English word?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2833,"timeElapsed":713022},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679532839,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":45,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":13839,"timeElapsed":728567},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679535636,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":46,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2795,"timeElapsed":731365},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679538450,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":47,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":2810,"timeElapsed":734179},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679541369,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":48,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2916,"timeElapsed":737098},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679546581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":49,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":5210,"timeElapsed":742310},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679561665,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":50,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":91,"rt":15083,"timeElapsed":757394},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679566107,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":51,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":96,"rt":4440,"timeElapsed":761836},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679574626,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":52,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":8516,"timeElapsed":770355},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679577661,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":53,"questionIdx":5,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"11","question":"In the space provided, take several minutes to tell your life story in as much detail as possible.","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":3032,"timeElapsed":773390},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679596479,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":54,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":68,"rt":15280,"timeElapsed":792208},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679600447,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":55,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":75,"rt":3967,"timeElapsed":796176},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679610581,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":56,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":36,"rt":10131,"timeElapsed":806310},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679615764,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":57,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":5180,"timeElapsed":811493},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679620916,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":58,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":5149,"timeElapsed":816645},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679626278,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":59,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":44,"rt":5360,"timeElapsed":822007},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679641359,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":60,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":34,"rt":15080,"timeElapsed":837088},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679652751,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":61,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":42,"rt":11391,"timeElapsed":848480},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679674316,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":62,"questionIdx":6,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"202","question":"Who was the last person you met up with outside your home or theirs? What did you do?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":40,"rt":21562,"timeElapsed":870045},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679697598,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":63,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":70,"rt":21563,"timeElapsed":893327},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679700875,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":64,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":92,"rt":3274,"timeElapsed":896604},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679704269,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":65,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":3392,"timeElapsed":899998},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679707696,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":66,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":71,"rt":3425,"timeElapsed":903425},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679710918,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":67,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":3221,"timeElapsed":906647},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679726712,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":68,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":72,"rt":15792,"timeElapsed":922441},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679730983,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":69,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":79,"rt":4270,"timeElapsed":926712},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679742694,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":70,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":59,"rt":11707,"timeElapsed":938423},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679746168,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":71,"questionIdx":7,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"243","question":"What kinds of things do you procrastinate on the most and why?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":3472,"timeElapsed":941897},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679767766,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":72,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":41,"rt":19662,"timeElapsed":963494},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679773901,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":73,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":66,"rt":6133,"timeElapsed":969630},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679781719,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":74,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":7817,"timeElapsed":977448},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679787785,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":75,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":39,"rt":6063,"timeElapsed":983514},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679790702,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":76,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":65,"rt":2915,"timeElapsed":986431},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679794643,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":77,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":38,"rt":3939,"timeElapsed":990372},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679797484,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":78,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":64,"rt":2839,"timeElapsed":993213},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679805489,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":79,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":54,"rt":8004,"timeElapsed":1001218},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679808884,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":8,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"201","question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"small talk","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":63,"rt":3393,"timeElapsed":1004613},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679814235,"comprehensionCheck":1,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":0,"trialIdx":80,"questionIdx":null,"scaleIdx":null,"questionID":null,"question":"When was the last time you went to the movies? What did you see? Did you like it?","questionCategory":"comprehension check","scaleID":null,"scaleBlock":null,"scaleText":"Please drag the slider all the way to the end labeled STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMin":"STRAWBERRY","scaleTextMax":"PINEAPPLE","sliderStart":50,"response":0,"rt":5350,"timeElapsed":1009964},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679831633,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":81,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":0,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":6,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think you would learn about them (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":15697,"timeElapsed":1027362},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679834304,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":82,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":1,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":7,"scaleBlock":3,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think they would learn about you (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":100,"rt":2669,"timeElapsed":1030032},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679838288,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":83,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":2,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":2,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How informative is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all informative","scaleTextMax":"Very informative","sliderStart":50,"response":60,"rt":3982,"timeElapsed":1034017},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679842573,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":84,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":3,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":3,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How deep is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all deep","scaleTextMax":"Very deep","sliderStart":50,"response":77,"rt":4283,"timeElapsed":1038302},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679846421,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":85,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":4,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":1,"scaleBlock":1,"scaleText":"How personal is this question?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all personal","scaleTextMax":"Very personal","sliderStart":50,"response":82,"rt":3845,"timeElapsed":1042150},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679860114,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":86,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":5,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":4,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how much do you think their answer would help you get to know them better (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":69,"rt":13691,"timeElapsed":1055843},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679871217,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":87,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":6,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":5,"scaleBlock":2,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how much do you think your answer would help them get to know you better (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all","scaleTextMax":"A lot","sliderStart":50,"response":94,"rt":11101,"timeElapsed":1066946},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679881303,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":88,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":7,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":8,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If you asked this question to someone you just met, how close would you feel with them upon hearing their answer (assuming they provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":58,"rt":10083,"timeElapsed":1077032},{"subjectID":"l0ehg0076g","prolificID":"67502684d9497056fc75185f","studyID":"675cbe11adb7edc5a4d1feca","sessionID":"67745b4b3190916f82d1dfc0","DEBUG":0,"trialSubmitTS":1735679886747,"comprehensionCheck":0,"comprehensionCheckRequestedResponse":null,"trialIdx":89,"questionIdx":9,"scaleIdx":8,"questionID":"58","question":"If you had to give away all of your money tomorrow, what cause or causes would you want to support? Why?","questionCategory":"personal","scaleID":9,"scaleBlock":4,"scaleText":"If someone you just met asked you this question, how close would you feel with them after sharing your answer (assuming you provided an honest answer)?","scaleTextMin":"Not at all close","scaleTextMax":"Very close","sliderStart":50,"response":78,"rt":5442,"timeElapsed":1082476}]